我真不敢相信你会这么说
I can't believe you'd actually say that.
我不是咸味先生而是花生先生
I'd much rather be Mr. Peanut than Mr. Salty.
才怪  咸味先生是个水手
No way. Mr. Salty is a sailor.
他应该是最强硬的点心
He's gotta be the toughest snack there is.
我说不好  你不会想和玉米作对的
I don't know. You don't wanna mess with Cornnuts.
它们简直是疯了
They're crazy.
上帝呀  你们应该看看这个
Oh, my God. You gotta come see this.
有个变态拿着望远镜
There's some creep out there with a telescope.
我真不敢相信他在看我们
I can't believe it. He's looking right at us.
真恶心
Oh, that is so sick.
我感觉被冒犯了
I feel violated.
而且很不爽
And not in a good way.
怎会有人这样
How can people do that?
你们看  丑裸男有双重力鞋
You guys, look. Ugly Naked Guy got gravity boots.
我跟你们说  几年后  学童将会把它
I'm telling you, years from now, school children will study it...
奉为首次约会完美案例研究
...as one of the greatest first dates of all time.
太令人难以置信了
It was unbelievable.
我们可以完全做自己  无须耍任何花招
We could totaly be ourselves. We didn't have to any play games.
你打过电话给她没
Have you called her yet?
让她知道我喜欢她  你疯了不成
Let her know I like her? What are you, insane?
-伙计  -太恶心了
- Guys. - It's gross.
才第二天  你要我显得多渴望
It's the next day. How needy do I wanna seem?
-我说的对吧  -对  让她悬着心吧
- I'm right. Right  - Yeah, let her dangle.
我无法相信我爸妈催着我找你们这种男人
I can't believe my parents are actually pushing me to find one of you people.
算了  行动吧
Come on. Just do it.
打给她  别这么大男子主义
Call her. Stop being so testosterone-y.
我得说一句  这还是旧金山特色
Which, by the way, is the real San Francisco treat.
-机器声  -她的答录机吗
- I got her machine. - Her answering machine?
不  有趣的是  她的落叶清扫机接的
No, interestingly, her leaf blower picked up.
那你为何不留言
So, why didn't you say anything?
不行  上次我想随意留两句话的时候
No. Last time I left a spontaneous message...
最后说了"对滴  是这样哦"
... I ended up using the phrase,"Yes,indeed-io."
看  是瑞秋和巴瑞
Look, it's Rachel and Barry.
不  大家别一起回头
No, don't everybody look at once!
怎么了
What's going on?
-他们只是在讲话  -他是否神情落寞
- They're just talking. - Does he look upset?
他是否像被告知滚远点的样子
Does he look like he was told to shove anything?
没有  其实他正在微笑
No. Actually, he's smiling.
我的老天  不要那样干
Oh, my God. Don't do that.
怎么啦  怎么啦  怎么啦
What? What? What?
对街的男人刚踢了一只鸽子
That man across the street just kicked that pigeon.
基本上  法案就是这么成为法律的
And basically, that's how a bill becomes a law.
懂了吗  嗨  瑞秋
See? Hey, Rach.
情况如何
How'd it go?
你们知道吗  其实感觉好极了
You know, it was actually really great.
他带我到俄罗斯茶室餐厅吃饭
He took me to lunch at the Russian Tea Room,
我点了那种一戳有奶油喷出来的鸡肉
I had that chicken, where you poke it and butter squirts out.
今天真不是鸟儿的好日子
Not a good day for birds.
然后我们一路走到本多尔商场
Then we took a walk down to Bendall's,
我告诉他不要  他还是买了香奈儿给我
And I told him not to,but he got me a bottle of Chanel.
真体贴  这是在你跟他说别再来电话
That's nice. Now was that before or after you told him...
别再送你花  别再来烦你之前还是之后
...to stop calling,stop sending flowers and to generally leave you alone?
老实说  我没机会开口
Right. Well, we never actually got to that.
能再见到他的感觉真好
It was just so nice to see him again.
感觉是那么自在而熟悉
It was comfortable and it was familiar.
感觉真好
It was just nice.
你已讲了两遍
That's nice twice.
瑞秋  这是怎么回事
Rachel, what's going on?
你难道忘了曾经在婚礼上抛弃巴瑞吗
Isn't this the same Barry who you left at the altar?
你上哪儿去了
Where have you been?
今天和他在一起感觉不同
It was different with him today.
他今天不像是牙医
He wasn't, like, Orthodontist Guy.
我们玩得很开心  这样有什么不对吗
I mean, we had fun. Is there anything wrong with that?
是的
Yes.
-为什么  -我有我的理由
- Why? - I have my reasons.
那么他订婚的对象刚好...
How about the fact that he's engaged to another woman...
是你曾经的好友这件事呢
...who happens to be your ex-best friend?
好吧  我知道这样做很傻
All right. I know it's stupid.
我下午会去找他谈分手
I'll see him this afternoon and put an end to it.
我没疯对吧  我们从未如此合拍过
I'm not crazy, right? I mean, it was never like that.
前所未有
No, it wasn't.
这儿有个小水槽真好
It was so nice having this little sink here.
丹妮尔  没想到是答录机接的
Oh, Danielle, I wasn't expecting the machine.
有空请回电
Give me a call when you get a chance.
再见
Bye-bye.
总算完了
Oh, God.
你两小时就憋出这么点词儿
That's what you've been working on for two hours?
我一直在演练呢
Hey, I've been honing.
-为什么拨弄盘子  -我要她以为我在餐厅
- What was with the dishes? - I want her to think I'm in a restaurant.
我过着不错的生活  而不是干坐在这里
I might have some kind of life. Like I haven't been sitting here...
演练了两个小时
... honing for the last two hours?
快看  又是他  那个拿望远镜的人.
Look look! He's doing it again, the guy with the telescope!
我的上帝
Oh, my God.
走开  别再往这儿看
Go away. Stop looking in here.
这下可好  他也挥手了
Great. Now he's waving back.
我们得想办法阻止他
We gotta do something about that guy.
早上我逮到他往我们公寓张望
This morning, I caught him looking into our apartment.
吓死我了  感觉自己没法做事
It creeps me out. I feel like I can't do stuff.
做什么事
What kind of stuff?
成熟点行吗  我不是指性
Will you grow up? I'm not talking about sexy stuff...
我只是不穿衣服做饭
...but, like, when I'm cooking naked.
你做饭不穿衣服吗
You cook naked?
对  烤土司  燕麦粥  别溅出来就行
Yeah, toast, oatmeal. Nothing that spatters.
看我干嘛  我毫不知情
What are you looking at me for? I didn't know that.
怎么了
What's the matter?
我只是  巴瑞  这样做不好
I just Oh, Barry, this was not good.
不  很好  是非常非常好
No, it was. It was very, very good.
-明蒂呢  -我们干得比明蒂好多了
- What about Mindy? - Oh, way, way better than Mindy.
不  我是指你和明蒂怎么办
I mean, what about you and Mindy?
如果你希望  那我就和她分手
If you want, I'll break it off with her.
万万不行  别那样做  别为我那样做
No, don't do that. Not for me.
范瑞柏医生  巴比·朗斯来做矫正了
Dr. Farber, Bobby Rush is here for his adjustment.
谢谢  波尼斯
Thanks, Bernice.
我们周末去度假吧
Let's go away this weekend.
巴瑞  这样也太...
Barry, come on, this is all way too...
不不不  我们可以去阿鲁巴岛
No, we can go to Aruba.
我上次是在我们本该有的"蜜月"去的
When I went there on what would've been our honeymoon...
感觉很棒  你一定会喜欢的
...it was really nice. You would've liked it.
我本来有穿胸罩
I had a bra.
嘿  范瑞柏大夫
Hey, Dr. Farber.
你好  格林小姐  看来一切正常
All right, Miss Greene, everything looks fine.
你的牙齿看来整齐许多嘛
We're starting to see some real progress.
-干嘛  -我12岁了  我不是傻子
- What? - I'm 12, I'm not stupid.
能借用你的电话吗
Can I use your phone?
我指点你一下  你拿的那支...
For future reference, that thing in your hand...
...也可以当电话使
...can also be used as a phone.
这电话没问题啊
Yes, it's working.
-她为何不回电  -或许她没听到你留言
- Why isn't she calling? - Maybe she never got your message.
如果愿意  你可以打给她的答录机
If you want, you call her machine,
如果听见许多哔声
and if she has a lot of beeps...
那代表她或许还没收留言
...that means she probably didn't get her messages yet.
你不认为这样会使我有点
Doesn't that make me seem?
绝望  迫切  可悲吗
Desperate? Needy? Pathetic?
你显然看过我的个人广告
You obviously saw my personal ad.
哔几声
How many beeps?
她接了
She answered.
此时你该向她打招呼才对
This is where you'd use that "hello" word.
我不能跟她讲话  她显然听到我的留言
I won't talk to her. She got my message...
而且选择不回电  我既迫切又被人冷落
...and is choosing not to call me. Now I'm needy and snubbed.
我真想念纯迫切的滋味
God, I miss just being needy.
他接受了吗
So how'd he take it?
事实上  还不错
Pretty well,actually.
瑞秋  你头发上为何有牙线
Rach. How come you have dental floss in your hair?
-有吗  -当然
- Oh, do l? - Uh, hmm.
我们以在他椅子上做爱告终
We ended up having sex in his chair.
你们在他椅子上做爱
You had sex in his chair?
我说得有点太大声了  是不是
I said that a little too loudly, didn't l?
你们做了什么
You had what?
在他椅子上做爱
Sex in his chair.
什么  你到底在想什么
What...? What were you thinking?
我不知道  我们仍在乎对方
I don't know. We still care about each other.
我们曾相爱过  就像你和卡罗尔一样
There's a history there. It's like you and Carol.
不  根本不像我和卡罗尔
No, it's nothing like me and Carol.
得了吧  如果她说
Please. If she said to you,
"罗斯  我此时只想和你在这沙发上缠绵"
"Ross,I want you on this couch... right here, right now,"
你会怎么回答
what would you say?
如果能帮你思考  我可以过去点
If it helps, I could slide over.
这完全是两回事  就像苹果和桔子
It's a totally different situation. It's apples and oranges.
是牙医和女同志的差别  我走了
It's orthodontists and lesbians. I gotta go.
-你要上哪儿去  -我就是要走  行吗
- Where are you going? - I just have to go, all right?
我需要理由吗  我有自己的人生要过
Do I need a reason? I have things to do with my life.
我有许多事要做
I have a jam-packed schedule.
我现在已经迟到了好吗
And I am late for keeping up with it, okay?
喂  喂
Hello? Hello?
喂
Hello?
明蒂啊
Mindy.
嗨  你好吗
Hi. How are you?
对  我听说了  恭喜  这真是太好了
Yes, I heard. Congratulations. That is so great.
真的  上帝啊
Really, oh, God
我明天要上班  但如果你愿意
I'm working tomorrow, but if you want,
可以到公司来一趟
you can come by if you'd like.
可以  太好了
Ok. Great.
太好了
Great.
那明天见了
So I'll see you tomorrow.
好的  再见
Okay. Bye.
天呀  天呀  天呀
Oh, God. Oh, God.
明蒂好吗
So how's Mindy?
她明天想见我  她的语调好诡异
She wants to see me tomorrow. She sounded weird.
我得打电话给巴瑞
I gotta call Barry.
是我  我只是...明蒂啊
It's me. I just...Mindy.
明蒂  不是  我一想你就在这
Mindy. No, I figured that's where you'd be.
你这种人都该下地狱
Hell is filled with people like you.
他又来了  偷窥狂又出现了
He's back. The peeper's back.
-蹲下  -蹲下干嘛
- Get down. - Get down?
接着跳舞
And boogie.
谢了  但我得去上班
Thanks, but I gotta go to work.
准备好被明蒂挠个满脸花
and get my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
放轻松  或许她都不知道
Relax. She may not even know.
我们七个月都没联络  她突然打电话来
I haven't heard from her in seven months, and now she calls me,
还会有什么事呢
what else is it about?
她曾是我最要好的朋友
She was my best friend.
我们一起去夏令营
We went to camp together,
-她教我如何亲吻  -是吗
- she taught me how to kiss... - Yeah?
如今  我像是成了第三者
Now, you know, I'm, like, the other woman.
-我感觉自己很  -顽皮
- I feel so - Naughty.
-回见了  -等等  我和你一起出去
- See you later. - Hold up. I'll walk with you.
瑞秋  她在夏令营时教你亲吻时
Rach. When she taught you to kiss, you were at camp,
你们有没有穿着制服  还是...
and.. were you wearing any kinda little uniform, or-
没事了
That's fine, yeah.
我要上洗手间  帮我守着电话好吗
I'm going to the bathroom. Will you watch my phone?
你何不带进去
Why don't you just take it with you.
我们还没第二次约会
We haven't had a second date...
她需要听到我尿尿的声音吗
...she needs to hear me pee?
为什么不打给她
Why don't you call her?
我留过言就不能打给她  我有自己的尊严
I can't call her. I left the message. I have some pride.
-有吗  -没有
- Do you? - No.
丹妮尔  嗨
Danielle, hi.
是我  钱德勒
It's Chandler.
我很好
I'm fine.
听着...
Listen....
我不知道你是否打过电话给我
I don't know if you tried to call me because...
因为我不小心把电话关了
... I accidentally shut off my phone.
没关系  太好了  好的
That's fine. That's great. Okay.
她正在讲电话  等一下回我电话
She's on the other line. She's gonna call me back.
She's on the other line,she's gonna call me back.
-你不想尿了吗  -所以我在跳舞
- Don't you have to pee? - That's why I'm dancing.
-明蒂  -嗨  你好
- Mindy. - Hey, you.
嗨  你好
Hey, you.
什么事
So what's up?
我们该坐下来谈
We should really be sitting for this.
当然啦
Sure we should.
我知道我们最近关系诡异
I know things have been weird...
但你是我认识最久的朋友
...but you're my oldest friend in the world,
除了萝瑞·沙弗之外
except for maybe Laurie Schaffer,
我现在也不跟她说话了
who I don't talk to anywhere,
因为她减肥成功后刻薄许多
...'cause she's all bitter now that she lost the weight...
但是脸蛋却依旧丑陋无比
...and it turns out,she doesn't have a pretty face.
-那我问了  -好的
- Okay, I'm just gonna say it. - Okay.
你愿意当我的伴娘吗
Will you be my maid of honor?
-当然  -太好了
- Of course. - That's so great.
-你就想问我这些  -对  就这些
- That's all you wanted to ask? - That's all.
-怎么了  -不只这样
- What? - That's not all.
-当然是的  -也不全是
- Oh, sure it is. -Oh, no, it isn't.
我认为巴瑞有其他的女人
I think Barry's seeing someone in the city.
你怎会这样想
What would make you think that?
宣布订婚后他就变了样
Ever since we announce the engagement, he's acted weird.
昨晚他回家时  身上有香奈儿的味道
And then last night, he came home smelling like Chanel.
真的
Really?
明蒂  如果这样能让你好过点
Mindy. If it'll make you feel any better...
我和巴瑞刚订婚时
...when Barry and I first got engaged,
他也像变了一个人  举止很奇怪
he went through a whole weird things too.
瞧  这就是我最担心的
Oh, God. You see that's what I was afraid of.
什么  你担心什么
What's what you were afraid of?
巴瑞和你订婚时  我跟他
When Barry was engaged to you, he and l...
正在偷偷恋爱
... kind of had a little thing on the side.
-什么  -我知道这不对
- What? - I know, I know.
他向我求婚时  每个人都劝我"别接受
When he proposed, everyone said "Don't do it,
他会像背叛瑞秋一样背叛你"
he's just gonna do to you what he did to Rachel,"
如今我觉得自己好傻
And now I feel so stupid.
明蒂  你真是傻
Oh Mindy. You are so stupid.
我们两个都傻透了
We are both so stupid.
什么意思
What do you mean?
味道熟悉吗
Smell familiar?
不是吧
Oh no.
真是抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry.
不  是我抱歉
Oh, no, me. I am so sorry.
不  我对不起  我抱歉
No, I am sorry. I'm sorry.
我的上帝
Oh, my.
四个字母  "圈圈或圆圈"
Four letters, "circle or hoop."
-快响[意同圆圈]  见鬼了  -谢啦
-Ring, damn it, ring. - Thanks.
-你知道我们的电话坏了不  -什么
- You know our phone's not working? - What?
我想从咖啡店打给你  但没有回音
I tried to call you from the coffee shop and there was no answer.
我关机了
I turned it off.
老天爷啊  我关机了
Mother of God, I turned it off.
和你告诉她的一样
Just like you told her you did.
只是指出槽点何在
Just pointing out the irony.
听着  我和对街门房谈过了
So listen, I went across the street to the doorman.
他告诉我那偷窥狂的名字  电话能借用吗
I got the peeper's name. Can I use the phone?
电话能借用吗
Can I use your phone?
请帮我查辛尼·马克斯的电话
The number for a Sidney Marks, please.
"取暖设备"
"Heating device."
散热器
Radiator.
俩字
Five letters.
"热器"
"Rdtor."
对  是辛尼吗
Yeah, is Sidney there?
你就是啊  辛尼是个女的
Oh, this is? Sidney's a woman.
是女的又怎样
So she's a woman, so what?
对  那又怎样
Yeah, so what?
听着  我住在对街
Look, I live across the street,
我注意到你拿望远镜偷窥
and I know about your telescope.
而且我很不喜欢你这样
And I don't appreciate it.
对  我现在就看得见你  喂
Yeah, I can see you right now. Hello?
如果我想在室内只穿内裤  我不该感觉
If I wanna walk around in my underwear,  I shouldn't have to feel
谢谢
Thank you.
那不是重点  重点是
That's not really the point. The point is, that
-我常举哑铃  偶尔也有...  -乔伊
- Mostly free-weights, but occasionally... - Joey!
对  我邻居  对  黑褐色头发
Yeah, my neighbor. Yeah, the brunette.
她说你那天穿绿色套装很好看
She said you looked pretty that day in the green dress.
绿色套装  真的吗
The green dress? Really?
对  她说你像英格丽褒曼
She said you looked like lngrid Bergman.
才没有
No.
-有空吗  -当然
- Hey. Got a second? - Sure, sure.
进来  吧
Come on...in...
你好  亲爱的
Hello, sweetheart.
你们来干什么
What you guys doing here?
我们是来和你分手的
We are here to break up with you.
你们两个一起
Both of you?
基本上我们认为你是个大烂人
Basically We think you're a horrible human being,
你该遭天谴
and bad things should happen to you.
对不起  我是个白痴
I'm sorry. God, I am so sorry.
我是个笨蛋  懦夫  我无法自拔
I'm a idot. I was weak. I couldn't help myself.
不管我做什么都是因为太爱你了
Whatever I did, I only did because I love you so much.
你说的是我俩谁
Which one of us are you talking to there?
明蒂
Mindy.
当然是指明蒂  我一直深爱着明蒂
Of course, Mindy. It was always Mindy.
我们在这把椅子上做爱时也是吗
Even when we were having sex in that chair?
我发誓  不论我做什么我都想着你
I swear, whatever I was doing, I was thinking of you.
拜托  第二回合时
Please. That second time,
你根本把她忘得一干二净了
you couldn't have picked her out of a lineup.
你们做了两次
You did it twice?
第一次不算  你了解巴瑞的
The first time didn't really count. You know, it was Barry.
亲爱的  甜心  再给我一次机会
Honey, sweetheart, look. Just give me another chance.
我们再重新来过  我们再到阿鲁巴岛去
We'll start over. We'll go back to Aruba.
范瑞柏医生  紧急状况
Dr. Farber, we've got an emergency here.
强森·卡斯特兰诺被自己的牙套噎到了
Jason Castalano's choking on his retainer.
天啊  我马上去  波尼斯
Oh, God. I'll be right there, Bernice.
求你了  求你别离开
Look, please, please don't go anywhere.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我们会在这儿的  恨你入骨
Okay, and we'll be here, hating you.
看见他走出去时满身大汗没
See how he was sweating when he walked out?
这样吧  我去抓住他那里
Listen honey, if I'm hogging the ball too much
然后你过去  狠狠打他几拳
you just jump right in there and take some punches.
我跟你说  那感觉一定很爽
because I'm telling you, this feels great.
是吗  我还是想嫁给她
Yeah? I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
明蒂  那家伙是个恶魔
Mindy, the guy is the devil.
是个衣冠禽兽
He is Satan in a smock.
我知道他并不完美
I know he's not perfect.
但事实是
But the truth is at the end of the day,
说到底我还是想当
I still really wanna be...
巴瑞·范瑞柏医生的
... Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber...
太太
... D.D.S.
我的天
Oh, God.
希望你能为我高兴
I hope you can find a way to be happy for me.
我希望你还愿意当我的伴娘
And I hope you'll still be my maid of honor.
我希望巴瑞不会在阿鲁巴岛将你宰了吃掉
And I hope Barry doesn't kill you and eat you in Aruba.
-你还好吗  -还好
- You okay? -Yeah.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
自从我在婚礼上抛下巴瑞
Since I ran out on Barry at the wedding...
我一直在想这决定是否正确
...I've wondered whether I made the right choice.
现在我知道了
And now I know.
我真为你高兴
I'm so glad.
好日子
Big day.
我告诉你  花生先生的穿着比较讲究
I'll give you this: Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
他有单片眼镜  高帽
He's got the monocle, he's got the top hat....
你知道他是个男同志吗
Did you know he's gay?
你说清楚了  这是要帮花生先生出柜吗
I just wanna clarify this. Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
-钱德勒  -丹妮尔  嗨
- Chandler? - Danielle, hi.
各位  这是丹妮尔  丹妮尔  这是大家
Everybody, this is Danielle. Danielle, everybody.
你为何会出现在这儿
What are you doing here?
我一直打电话给你  结果我记错号码了
I've been calling you, it turns out that I had your number wrong.
最后总算问查号台知道你的号码
When I finally got the right one from the information,
却没人接电话
there was no answer.
我想来看看你是否无恙
So I thought I'd come down here and make sure you were okay.
我没事
I'm okay.
或许我们改天可以见个面
Maybe we could get together later?
这主意不错  我再打给你
That sounds good. I'll call you.
或是你打给我  都行
Or you call me, whatever.
一言为定
You got it.
-再见了  各位  -再见
- Bye, everybody. - Bye.
-干得好  -第二次约会
- There you go. - Second date.
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道
You don't know?
她好像很不错
She seems nice any enerything,
但她大老远来这儿
but the whole thing about her coming all the way here...
只想确定我没事  有这必要吗
...just to see if I was okay? I mean, how needy is that?